<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BetterVia</string>
    <string name="select_language">选择语言 / Select Language</string>
    <string name="auto_select">自动选择 (Automatic Selection)</string>
    <string name="simplified_chinese">简体中文</string>
    <string name="traditional_chinese">繁體中文</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="agreement_title">Software Agreement</string>
    <string name="agree_button">I have read and agree</string>
    <string name="disagree_button">Disagree and Exit</string>
    <string name="agreement_content">Author: JiGuro (hereinafter referred to as \"I\" or \"the declarant\") \nWelcome to the \"BetterVia\" module (hereinafter referred to as \"this software\"), a tool for researching scope software (hereinafter referred to as \"Hook software\"). Before using this software, please ensure you have carefully read, fully understood, and agreed to the Software Usage Declaration (hereinafter referred to as \"this declaration\"). Minors must read, understand, and agree to this Statement under the guidance of a legal guardian before using this software. If you disagree with any part of this Statement, please refrain from using this software. \nThe code for this software was collected and organized by the Author from publicly available third-party sources on the internet and is shared solely for technical exchange. In accordance with the relevant provisions of the Regulations of the People\'s Republic of China on the Protection of Computer Software, this software is intended solely for learning and researching the design concepts and principles of software. Its use for any commercial or illegal purposes is strictly prohibited. Once the learning or research objective is achieved, or if the user decides to discontinue its use for such purposes, the software must be permanently deleted from storage devices. Users must ensure their usage complies with relevant laws and regulations, including the Copyright Law of the People\'s Republic of China, the Regulations on the Protection of Computer Software of the People\'s Republic of China, the Cybersecurity Law of the People\'s Republic of China, the Data Security Law of the People\'s Republic of China, and the Personal Information Protection Law of the People\'s Republic of China. All legal liabilities shall be borne solely by the user. \nIntellectual property is strictly protected by law; please refrain from infringement. If the software being hooked by this tool incorporates or is based on open-source software, users must also comply with the terms of the relevant open-source licenses when using this software. I advocate for and strongly support the use of licensed software. Using licensed software not only ensures a positive user experience and stable performance but also demonstrates respect and support for the innovation and efforts of software developers. If you find the hooking software helpful or appreciate it, please actively support licensed versions. \nIt is hereby explicitly emphasized that this software is shared solely for educational and exchange purposes, without any profit-making intent. Users should fully recognize that due to the third-party nature of the software\'s source code and the limitations of my capabilities, I cannot provide any form of guarantee or warranty regarding the software\'s security (including but not limited to the absence of computer viruses, malicious code, backdoor programs, security vulnerabilities, or privacy-invading features) or legality (such as copyright status). Under no circumstances shall the declarant be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, punitive, or consequential damages (including but not limited to data loss, system damage, business interruption, loss of profits, privacy breaches, legal disputes, etc.) arising from the download, installation, use, inability to use, or reliance on this software. This applies regardless of whether such liability arises from contract, tort (including negligence), strict liability, or any other legal theory, and regardless of whether the declarant was previously informed of the possibility of such damages. I strongly advise users to discontinue using this module and obtain genuine software through official channels provided by the software developer to ensure security and legality. I affirm that during the sharing of this software, I have not intentionally implanted any computer viruses or backdoor programs, nor have I deliberately incorporated any features designed to infringe upon user privacy. Should users discover any such issues in this software, they must promptly contact me. I will immediately take measures such as deletion to resolutely prevent further dissemination of this software. \nUpon first running this software, users will be required to fully read this statement through the interactive interface provided (e.g., pop-up window) and must actively select options such as \"Agree\" or \"I Understand\" to explicitly consent to its contents. By running or continuing to use this software, users are deemed to have carefully read, fully understood, and agreed to accept all terms of this statement, voluntarily assuming all legal liabilities and consequences arising from downloading, installing, or using this software. Please use this software lawfully to jointly maintain a healthy online environment and legal order. The final interpretation of this statement rests solely with the declarant.</string>
    <string name="toast_agreement_required">Please agree to the user agreement to continue</string>
    <string name="by_author">By JiGuro</string>
    <string name="blog_link">My Blog</string>
    <string name="contact_email">Contact Me</string>
    <string name="module_status">Module Status</string>
    <string name="activated">Activated</string>
    <string name="not_activated">Not Activated</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="security_fix">Security Fix</string>
    <string name="hide_icon">Hide Desktop Icon</string>
    <string name="show_icon">Show Desktop Icon</string>
    <string name="toast_icon_hidden">Icon hidden</string>
    <string name="toast_icon_shown">Icon shown</string>
    <string name="toast_operation_failed">Operation failed</string>
    <string name="toast_permission_denied">Operation failed: Permission denied</string>
    <string name="toast_cannot_open_github">Cannot open GitHub</string>
    <string name="toast_cannot_open_gitee">Cannot open Gitee</string>
    <string name="toast_cannot_open_xposed">Cannot open Xposed repository</string>
    <string name="toast_cannot_open_link">Cannot open link</string>
    <string name="toast_cannot_send_email">Cannot send email</string>
    <string name="blog_url">https://jigurolgc.github.io</string>
    <string name="email_address">jigurolui@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="version_info">BetterVia v1.2.0</string>
    <string name="copyright_info">Not For Commercial Use</string>
    <string name="withdraw_agreement">Withdraw Agreement</string>
    <string name="withdraw_agreement_title">Withdraw Agreement</string>
    <string name="withdraw_agreement_message">Are you sure you want to withdraw your agreement? This will reset the app and you will need to agree to the terms again on next launch.</string>
    <string name="withdraw_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="withdraw_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="withdraw_success">Agreement withdrawn, app will now exit</string>
    <string name="update_settings">Update Settings</string>
	<string name="auto_check_updates">Auto Check Updates</string>
	<string name="select_update_source">Select Update Source</string>
	<string name="github">GitHub</string>
	<string name="gitee">Gitee</string>
	<string name="new_version_found">New version found: v%1$s</string>
	<string name="download_now">Download Now</string>
	<string name="later">Later</string>
	<string name="cannot_open_download_link">Cannot open download link</string>
	<string name="update_check_failed">Update check failed</string>
	<string name="already_latest_version">Already the latest version</string>
	<string name="checking_updates">Checking for updates...</string>
	<string name="update_source_description">Selecting an update source affects the speed and success rate of update checks</string>
	<string name="security_fix_dialog_title">Security Fix</string>
	<string name="security_fix_dialog_message">This mode is designed to fix module restricted functions and requires Root permission or file read/write permissions. To use Root permission, you may need to remove Root hiding for BetterVia in advance.\n\nAre you sure you want to continue the repair?</string>
	<string name="security_fix_success">Security fix completed, module restrictions have been removed</string>
	<string name="security_fix_no_issue">No configuration issues detected</string>
	<string name="security_fix_need_permission">Root permission or file read/write permissions are required to perform the repair</string>
	<string name="security_fix_storage_permission_denied">Please grant file read/write permissions</string>
	<string name="security_fix_suggest_root">If there are still issues, consider using Root permission to repair again</string>
	<string name="root_permission_granted">Root permission granted successfully</string>
	<string name="root_permission_denied">Root permission denied, please try to remove Root hiding for BetterVia</string>
	<string name="tamper_dialog_title">Security Detection Exception</string>
	<string name="tamper_dialog_message">Application modification detected or security risk exists!\nFor your system security, the program will exit automatically.\nPlease download the official version or clear storage and try again.</string>
	<string name="description">让Via变得更好\nMake Via Better</string>
</resources>
